<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KOWFAM</title>
    <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/authors/helenandryan/</link>
    <description>Recent content on KOWFAM</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 05:54:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.kowfam.uk/authors/helenandryan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Venice Day 12</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/04/italy-2019-venice-day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/04/italy-2019-venice-day-12/</guid>
      <description>After a lie in (so late, we missed breakfast - the holiday appears to have taken it out of us!), we walked around Venice for a bit before stopping for a pastry and coffee.
Then, we enjoyed our last gelato (sad times) and walked around some more. We like Venice a lot, but Florence is still our favourite city.
After that, we caught the water taxi to the airport, where we made the most of the free snacks and drinks with our lounge passes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Venice Day 11</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/03/italy-2019-venice-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/03/italy-2019-venice-day-11/</guid>
      <description>First thing this morning, we enjoyed watermelon for breakfast while taking in the epic view from our Airbnb one last time.
And, once we’d checked out and refuelled the car, we hunted down some more breakfast plus coffee at a spot called La Cremerie in Peschiera del Garda.
After all of that, we finally hit the road heading towards Venice, arriving around midday. We dropped the car off and then got the water taxi into the city centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Lake Garda Day 10</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/02/italy-2019-lake-garda-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/02/italy-2019-lake-garda-day-10/</guid>
      <description>First thing this morning, we drove to Malcesine, a town to the northeast of Lake Garda. Once there, we stopped for breakfast before taking in some of the views.
Then, we rode two cable cars up to Monte Baldo, which is a mountain range in the Italian Alps. We walked up to the peak, where we were even higher than clouds and you could see for miles. There were even some goats and alpacas (!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Lake Garda Day 9</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/01/italy-2019-lake-garda-day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/08/01/italy-2019-lake-garda-day-9/</guid>
      <description>Once we’d munched some anguria for breakfast, we hit the road heading north towards our next destination, Lake Garda, which is the largest lake in Italy. The journey took us through mountains and very picturesque scenery.
Along the way, we stopped off a couple of times for some coffee and crisps!
We arrived at Sirmione, a small town to the south of Lake Garda, in the early afternoon. The town is very beautiful and the water is crystal clear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Cinque Terre Day 8</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/31/italy-2019-cinque-terre-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/31/italy-2019-cinque-terre-day-8/</guid>
      <description>Following a watermelon breakfast in our Airbnb, we boarded a (very busy and hot!) train to the northernmost village of the five villages that make up the Cinque Terre, Monterosso al Mare.
Once there, we stopped off for a coffee and some olive focaccia by the beach.
After that, we trained it to the next village, Vernazza. This one was much prettier and more interesting with its colourful houses.
There is a 12km coastal hike joining all 5 villages which we had read about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - La Spezia Day 7</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/30/italy-2019-la-spezia-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/30/italy-2019-la-spezia-day-7/</guid>
      <description>Following pastries, coffee, and watermelon for breakfast, we picked up our hire car ready for our next destination, La Spezia/Cinque Terre! It was stressful driving through the very narrow streets of Florence to get out of the city, especially when you’re sitting on the wrong side of the car (thanks, Napoleon!). But once we hit the motorway, it was much easier.
We decided to stop off at Pisa to see the leaning tower and get some pizza at Pisa for lunch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Florence Day 6</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/29/italy-2019-florence-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/29/italy-2019-florence-day-6/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of a lie in, we enjoyed pastries and coffee for breakfast, followed up with some Italian dark chocolates!
Our first destination of the day was Giotto’s Bell Tower. We had to climb 414 steps to get to the top and it was very narrow like the last tower we climbed in Rome! But the views were great.
After that, we went into The Baptistery of St. John, which was built 1059-1128.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Florence Day 5</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/28/italy-2019-florence-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/28/italy-2019-florence-day-5/</guid>
      <description>After another epic breakfast, we checked out of our hotel and boarded the train (just in time!) to Florence. The trains here are much more spacious and comfortable than the ones we’re used to at home, and there was plenty of air conditioning, too. We were a bit sad to be leaving Rome, as we’ve had some of the best experiences here. But we were looking forward to exploring a new place!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Rome Day 4</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/27/italy-2019-rome-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 05:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/27/italy-2019-rome-day-4/</guid>
      <description>After a repeat of yesterday’s breakfast (and a stocking up on pants and socks at the local H&amp;amp;M!), we headed to the Roman Forum, the heart of the ancient city of Rome. Apparently, it all used to be marshlands, which we found hard to believe given the heat!
On the way back to the hotel to freshen up, we had to stop for some ice cream at Grezzo again because it was so good!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Rome Day 3</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/26/italy-2019-rome-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 21:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/26/italy-2019-rome-day-3/</guid>
      <description>After a later start and hearty birthday breakfast of pastries, potatoes, cakes, and fruit, Helen opened the rest of her presents before we headed via the metro to our first destination of the day, St. Peter’s Basilica. Thanks to Helen’s organisation skills, we skipped the very long line with advance tickets!
All the decor and detail in the basilica was breathtaking. We decided to climb the 551 steps to the top of the Dome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Rome Day 2</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/25/italy-2019-rome-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 21:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/25/italy-2019-rome-day-2/</guid>
      <description>After another early start (5:30AM - FML), we headed from our hotel through the centre of Rome to board our coach trip! Our first stop along the way was Cassino for a (very strong!) americano, plus a croissant.
Afterwards, we ventured up windy (and very narrow - especially for such a big coach!) roads up to Mount Vesuvius, taking in the beautiful and classic Italian scenery, including the city of Naples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy 2019 - Rome Day 1</title>
      <link>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/24/italy-2019-rome-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 11:58:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.kowfam.uk/2019/07/24/italy-2019-rome-day-1/</guid>
      <description>After a tearful and eventful (he threw up in the car on the way to the cat hotel!) goodbye to Diego yesterday afternoon, we headed to Heathrow, stopping off at Pizza Express for dinner on the way.
We stayed at the Sofitel Hotel at Heathrow Terminal 5 (which was very nice!) and ordered a couple of mocktails to have in our room while Helen opened a couple of her birthday presents early!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>